Voices collide, the storm and the flame
Laughter and chaos, it's part of the game
Secrets unravel, the stage is alive
In Psyche's arena, the strange will survive
Who's awake? We're awake
Who's afraid? Let it break
From shadows to starlight, the truth will be shown
The Psyche awakens, you're never
be unexpected
Strange and unusual step inside the flow the circus of shadows it's psyches show
Terrible trolls in the dark take their stand, but angels are dancing torchlight in head
psyche's show terrible trolls in the dark take their stand the angels are dancing torchlight in
hand let's start the show
readings oh are we all up yeah hey what's up here we go uh oh well hi what a resplendent intro
great AI intro
Thank you. I'll behave
Okay. Thank you. Appreciate that. Asalaamu alaykum. I'll just
You're the conch. Awesome. I mean
so look can I just be no
End slurs word. Yes. No N word, please. Let me just tell you these assholes
Shaniqua's Tyrell's whatever
and there's this white, sorry, I'll just say this,
they're flagging me, Psyche, to the point of where
I've just got to make videos on Bitshoot and Rumble,
but it's okay, it's a hobby,
I'm getting back to work in the insurance world.
I will not say slurs, there are good people
of all groups, we love everybody, I'm dressed,
my friend said I look like a camel shit,
and I said, well, hududu, that's the closest I'll come.
I've been drinking for seven hours
Even the Nazis are sick of me and I'm sick a lot of them too. My audience sucks. Not my audience is cool
I want them to see this
All right, what's the topic you're gonna love ghosts ghosts. This is reviler. He likes to debate
Reviled yeah, what's the topic though? Sorry. Well ghosts will name it
We have a copy. Don't fuck you just join
all is this some other anonymous assholes just fuck you
oh my name is John
I really don't care asshole if you're not showing your face
he likes to debate
I don't care
he'll obey anything
I don't care dude
you can't give him
then let him talk
come on
it's not good
you don't know what the fuck you're talking about
Sir you're some anonymous asshole that I've never met before and you're calling me
Why don't you get on camera asshole is this a stupid retard drama
Like a dead
Okay, you literally just said it. You don't fuck
Where they say that like 500 times
Hey, hey, don't do that asshole. I'm gonna kick you out forever. Okay, don't do it again. I didn't
Oh god, here we go
Sorry, yeah, I was pretty bad to you in the past I understand that look I just like if you're gonna call me names
Just like have a point. That's all I ask. I just don't know who this guy
He doesn't really have a debate subject
Okay, I have a debate topic for you guys
Go ahead and I'm gonna assign the side that you have to debate. So is water wet or does it just get other things wet?
Sorry one more time. Sorry is water wet or does it just make other things wet?
Okay
If there was one drop of water and then another drop is that two drops is equal on bigger
Yeah, how about let's debate on AI is AI creativity really creativity? I think
We should talk about like these only fan models. I think AI is really I think that's the big problem
They're gonna take over the sect a sex injury
Injury like like they're gonna take over like because there's like some like weird
Half those only pancakes, they just, you just have a video streaming over and over and over looping.
It's, it's revitalized red.
There's a little name tag, it says revitalize red.
Hey brother, what's your name?
Red? Or what's your name?
Red.
Yeah, it's just red, it's fine.
Can I call you red? Do you mind if I call you red?
No, go ahead dude. If you want to talk like a person, I'll talk to that person, bro, go ahead.
And yeah, don't get psyching in trouble guys. He's, for degenerate, he's a nice guy. Go ahead.
For degenerate. How's he degenerate? Go ahead.
Nothing. He just, he doesn't recycle as much as he should. That's why. Go ahead. What were you gonna
ask? Yeah, but you just, you literally just made that claim. He's a degenerate.
So therefore the plan would roll with you know fuck don't know you just made that claim. So you're just like unstable
Okay, that's cool. I don't know who you are sir like I obviously a lot of my
I have a good topic. I have a good topic you guys
I'm going to give you something to talk about. Okay? Spurr out emotionally. You have no logical points. The girl's more
or is it universal, morality?
I think it's universal and let me explain why.
I think like, even if you're not religious
or anything like that, you don't,
you get your moral sort of parents,
their parents get it from their parents,
their parents get it, it comes from somewhere.
And I think ultimately it comes down to,
I'm interested to see what red things because he does have
Yeah, well, you're gonna spur get and chimp out anyway like a low IQ Tyrell anyway
Even if you get your morals from your parents, that's great what makes Ahmed's more
the
You don't have to mute so if you get your morals from your parents
Where do where do they get their morals from and then where do their parents get their morals from and then?
Where do their parents get their morals from?
That right, but that their parents
Wait, wait a minute, so okay, so but I'm saying though are you like okay real quick dude like insults whatever bullshit aside
I understand the shit
No, but really all that aside and hominems aside right because we're actually having a like a discord now
So are you okay, but like
So we obviously acknowledge that things like temperature, right, hot or cold, what we would perceive, we can test with thermometers, shit like that, cook food, freeze food. We acknowledge that, right? As dumb as this sounds, go with me. Like, we acknowledge that, right? That's objective.
Dude, I'm following the logic. Go ahead.
Okay, all right. So whatever you think about freezing or burning shit, like, we can do it, like.
Invariably we can do it now the problem with something like morals or religion which psyche doesn't like to offend people
We won't get into that. I'm doing a parody
Okay, so so so real quick though like so I guess when the girl's asking like are they universal
I guess we should she should have asked it's good question, but she should have asked like are they object are they objective?
So I call you ty or crew
Yeah, come he goes or call me T. Call me T. Y. Whatever you want. All right
So now we're over the stupid petty bullshit trash in each other. So we're so we're really talking here. So
Fuck the chat if you guys don't rely on the chat school overall, but like fuck the chat. I'm on bitch
No, that's fine. So just so just real quick like do we
Because I'm an ethical nihilist. I know that morals are man-made abstract ideas, like the idea of quote
good art or God or something like that, that gets into other ship. But like, what about you?
Like, do you think morals can be even in... Let me ask you this though, and it might be a stupid
question to you, sir. I'm asking you, by the way. Uh, like, do you think like a greater power
I would just say mother nature. I grew I grew up Catholic learning just as they go all that shit
But like I left yeah left that one was like 20, you know, I just I don't trust Abrahamic religions
No offense to any of them. They're just none of them
Yeah, go ahead sir. I'm sorry to talk to you. No Matt. Yeah, like it sounds like without being dicks to each other
We have a bit more in common even if you are anonymous faced right here. That's fine. Yeah, right here in disagreeing debate
I love this shit. I live for this shit. Um, yeah, so yeah, but with morals, let's just stick on that dude
And I don't mean to interrupt. Yeah
And I think like morals like you get it
It's kind of taught to you, but it's kind of taught by like I would you agree like your parents?
Yeah, but what makes them fucking right?
I mean you break it down enough. It's gonna come from somewhere brother
Okay, it has to come from somewhere. Okay, but but like that's it's not the somewhere like temperature though
Would you not and again the girl the vtuber cute cartoon person or psyche looking good by the way psyche or keeping the pounds
No, that's fine, ma'am
But if you don't mind having a conversation with me, I'm down to half. No, I don't
Yeah, she's definitely feel free to join in here and let the chat trash us all they want go in
Screw you chat, I'm kidding
I think people should innately have morals and that they should hold themselves to a standard, but people don't always have that, but where do they get them from, you get them from their parent, and where do your parents get them from, they get them from somewhere, from parents and parents.
So that would be an argument for it's a social construct, morals.
Is that a fallacy? Am I bringing up a fallacy right now?
No, I'm pretty sure you
It's gonna come from so unless I'm bringing up a fallacy
You let her like put out her whole point though like she was trying to like she's like in the middle
It's letter complete the point and then go ahead
For it being a social construct
And also the fact that morals kind they progress they evolve so slavery used to be okay, but as we evolved
Well
For yourself
Every single like skin color used to be in slavery, you know that right over the history of the world
Nope, I'm talking about there's all different kinds to say in general human service
Human servitude is no longer. Okay, so morals evolved. Okay. Sorry just to get more
Can I still have the conversation with him if you guys don't mind
go ahead it's fine hold on dude what crew crew crew I'm pretty drunk man here
let's everybody I want to talk yeah I understand that hold on but for what
she just said so here's the problem I have
we're having a conversation go so we got to listen to everybody real quickly and it's like
he's panel but we're quick man so the problem the only problem I have is not what she said
it's kind of with all of you and then myself I'll say it the meta analysis behind this right
like we get like the behind right we gave the fucking temperature the temperature gauge right
but the problem with her and you and everybody I want to and even him
there's no way like she said slavery is considered a moral now well yes if you were in the late 1700s
no not so much right that the wolf family and everything right they made a lot of money on
this trip the portuguese a lot of people right and then the trans-saharan slave trade and like
ottoman empire all types of shit even we won't get into all the controversies of that but not
with standing there's nothing that made slavery actually right or wrong and i'm going to be an
I'm gonna say this. I think everybody here is I gotta be real careful. I don't want to get this guy flagged
I think everybody here and myself is again
Let's just say child acts right like per people will call it perverse
But but but can I as an ethical nihilist say that it's wrong?
No, I can say it's damaging objectively to
things I won't elaborate on to stick things were in someone small and hurt them like that. That's
not good for the species. You know, that's that's not the same as like dogs or cats in breeding
or something like that, even at their age or maturity, which probably is not good for them
genetically either. I don't know. Yeah, he, well, yes, with Aisha, according to Sahih,
we won't do that because do it if you follow me
and I need to know what you're talking about
yeah we're bringing that up
I know all about
and why do you think I'm dressed like this man
I ordered this for a reason
wait I'm just saying
we can say
that certain things are damaging
we can say that certain things are productive in creation
but we cannot say things are wrong
So I don't do real quick. Hold on man. I'm just I'm not trying to be rude, dude
So again, we got the rudeness to be in fucking dickheads to each other now. We're having a real talk now
I mean, I agree, but I I'm not trying to say that on this guy's stream
Yeah, it's psyche. Why don't you just mute one person while the other one's talking
I just want to ask you guys, like temperature.
we can measure centigrade, we can measure Fahrenheit, we can measure Celsius, right?
Take a thermometer, feel it on your skin.
What is the meta how we can measure morals?
What you will find that morals like religions and philosophical schemas for the most part
are in our minds.
Prove that they're not fucking abstract.
I can answer that like
So like if your parents felt like you know, they felt the heat of the Sun and it was like hot
Or that maybe they even put their hand over a fire and it was hot
You know, if it was hot they probably wouldn't stick their fucking hand over it again
So like your parents looked it and then your parents looked it and their parents looked it and their parents looked it
So we're trying to say I don't know why you're trying to wear on what you
You're wearing cuz I thought we were gonna actually have like a really real debate
I am I'm not no I don't believe in any man-made somatic religion or any religion period look dude. I just want to say this
You're right about that
You're I was troll I did my own fucking stream on a banned website for like fucking six
No, I don't get many views at all
the
I I'm gone. I like a lot of people talk, you know, I'm enjoying talking to you
Listen, so if you fucking if your parents, yeah, your parents and they learn from there back to the fucking like Crow Magnans
Whatever the fuck right?
You're wearing something
Amazon it's it was a joke
It's a it's a it's a camel shit hat, but I can't I'm trying to not
I'm talking to you.
that's ironic is your truck I'm trying to tell you dude I understand what you're saying that you're talking though sir about the physical implication of that your parents and everybody learned from fire hey man don't touch burning fire right fair enough I'm I put your answer to fire you don't fuck you're talking about they have to get their muscle somewhere do they not
ghosts and I do like ghosts overall and even if they think I'm a double agent, whatever
the fuck, listen, ghost, here's the thing, man, you're correct on a physical level.
All right.
I don't think anybody's fucking denying that.
The problem is this, we go fire can burn you real, real, real effects, right?
But morals, that's completely subjective.
Morals in the fucking 14th century and, you know, like middle ages, Spain are very different
than modern Spain, right?
What how do we gauge that because fire was always hot right fire is probably
so I'm saying
Generations and generations I know but fire came to burn people from generations bro
But what the fuck about abstract ideas that change with time?
Those are not the same mate. Those are not the same as your parents burning with fire you great great great
That real quick so we nice to get them like a like a point here. What's your words you?
you just don't give a fuck
no, we're just animals and some species of animals are better
no, but wait, this doesn't address that morals are subjective
can you take a multi-meter and measure a moral and show me that Christianity or Islam or homosexuality or against homosexuality
yeah, I can take anything you want and I can show you that Christian
Uh, like ethics against it. Yes. If it's bad, listen when I'm talking if it's morally bad because it's against I can literally show that and if it's morally good, I can literally show that because I have a Christian ethics against it.
Okay, but you're yeah, but you're Christian ethics, which I used to believe you're talking about
He's my good friend and he is gay
You're saying it's a degenerate so that's that's you're saying but then you're saying we're animals and so there's no moral judgment there, right?
So well, yeah, right
Well, no, that's it. No, there is no judgment. No, fuck that. No, no, there is more. Okay. Look, fuck
I was like you ever only whoever's doing what real quick before I fucking mute ghost you're saying this according to Christianity
You do realize without offending anybody as much as I came that
Christianity and Islam that came later literally took from the Torah
No, wait, man, dude, you do don't interrupt me broader
the
I don't like I okay. Thanks. Well, then I'll shut up for you
Listen, man, is that where does your fucking Old Testament come from the Torah? It comes from the Pentateuch, okay?
It comes from the Hebrew before the fucking Greek the first Septuagint from the third to first century BCE so that Jews in
That fucking area could read Greek and Alexandria in Egypt, right? So your religion came after them
Okay, Judaism was before that and again
I do not get a lot of friends defending Jews these days, trust me, especially my fucking
past.
He's very hot.
but I'm what I'm just saying it's easy to blame them for everything right I'm
with but all I'm saying man is you can't you can say that you have those
Christian convictions
I'm actually saying things that are contradicting your simplistic world view
that's cool so why did you go from the Torah and pervert the fucking Hebrew and
turn like Almond's a Betulon Parthenos bro and really quickly how can you prove
those Christian morals if you stole from Jews and they don't believe in your
I don't I don't I don't I don't
go just to address what I said man that's all even if christianity or judeism or islam or whatever it's like
prove that it's right man you can't
i understand you look i don't want to hear my song i want to hear you talk to man i don't think you're a
totally dumb guy okay listen dude we were getting somewhere and then you go off this christian
shit i understand but not everybody's a fucking christian not everybody i'm dressed like a muslim
as a fucking joke you think i'm a fan of them i got kicked off of youtube and everything the nazis hate me
You know when you're in like AA, like alcohol, alcohol anomalous?
I'm not a fan of that.
And they say like, you know, they say that prayer, you know, they don't say God.
You know, they say like, they believe in a higher power.
Okay.
Do you believe in a higher power?
no way hold on dude I will answer your question but I gotta tell you I gotta tell you man
he said he's a nihilist he doesn't believe in anything
dude I'm meeting this with all due respect to this other white man here this the fucking ghost guy
listen dude you're fucking prevaricating and you're what you're doing is you're running around my
questions so I and I'll answer your question exactly my question is that you're correct about
about fire you're correct because there's a physical implication there but
about morals that shits all in our heads can you prove that wrong using science
or nature that's all any of you go ahead that's all I know listen let me
answer the question can I not answer yeah I was just gonna say that how about
Hey, don't the personal attack and don't use that word. Come on
I think I would take it to like, uh,
And I had to be like this because well, I don't want to do it because he's gonna end the stream
You put you promised a panel go see if I can stop saying the end word
Like you don't end the shit man
I shouldn't have said a bad precedent for psyche you got up
Well, fuck it. I want my 20 bucks then you guys don't feel like it goes
Ghost I just want to hear how morals are somehow real like what measurement can we use for them?
Well, listen, I think I I think that's a good question. I think you should
I think that is a good question. I think you should challenge it
Um, you can base it on if your actions hurt other people
Well, listen, I was yeah, you good point. That was a good point
No, because that's utilitarianism and that's not necessarily true because some people don't value helping
Listen, I think I think there's a great argument. I forget what it's called though. I want to Google it, but I'm fucking
I'm not a debater and I'm retarded. Oh, I can't say that. I'm dumb dumb. I'm dumb dumb
This new guy here for proving once and for all ghosts cannot debate
He's trying to bring up simple topics like nature versus nurture, but he's too dumb to even do that
A ghost, you really, really suck at this.
And I want to thank the guys for proving it.
All right, now I'm going to have to talk to people.
I'm going to have to shut up, and I'm going to say,
oh, I'm going to bring up the beaters.
Go ahead.
He's got to learn somehow.
Go ahead, DeBurne, so we're learning now.
You're pretty dumb, guys, and you've proven that today
this morning, and I want to thank this fellow
for letting everyone know it.
Nature versus nurture. This is I mean this topic's been around since day one and you're too dumb
You're not listening to this gentleman, you're just waiting for your turn to talk you suck at this absolutely
knows
Everyone in chat knows it now. You stink now. Donate more money because you're too fucking stupid to have the conversation
Yeah, I'm the damn one. I want you to go back once this is done
I
You're hurt you sound like an idiot, dude, you really do
You're an idiot and thank you for proving that uh, everyone have a great morning
Are you gonna go this quickly? Like, can you not stay? Okay, he's gone. Okay.
Okay, did anybody prove that somehow magically or not magically actually quite the inverse like
Naturalistically that morals are real. That's all not again fire burns you don't touch fire a good idea, but I'm talking about
Homosexuality is right or home homosexuality. Are you talking to me or the guy dude? Come on, man
Like I'm not
He just acts like a baby
I'll get your baby, you're a good part of me, I'm just a baby.
then well this then
Goes goes you're just an asshole because you're not bright enough to engage
No, if you if I'm the retard then
You're bipolar like you go from insulting people and acting like a spurg chimping out to like being a reasonable guy
So which is it?
Okay
I know it's so fucking horrible, like process language, right, process language, I know I'm just an insurance salesman by day, I'm just a retard, what do I know, right?
You can't talk like those fucking idiots.
I wouldn't say retard.
can you prove morals
I don't care if I'm at our word
yeah I think I can prove moral
okay go ahead because Christianity
I'm not a true religion either
but millions of people believe it
let this asshole is a low IQ
asshole answer go ahead
you gotta let me talk though
I'm fucking asking people bro if they can
prove
I was talking asshole this guy is a fucking asshole you should kick this guy else like
You're probably on SSI, like a typical mentally ill piece of shit.
Prove morals, prove morals, prove morals, prove morals, prove morals, do it, prove it, prove a
muscle. Can I say something?
Yeah, prove morals because they're a human concept, that's the difference between animals and humans.
Precisely, they're not our hat, but he's gonna prove them, Psyche.
Animals don't think about that.
No, he's a genius, let him prove it, mate, he's a genius on let him prove it.
Well, we're in a perfect never be on me. I never once made that claim his answer is Christian
You thought you had me but she didn't you fucking
Ghost
I
Want to talk to me bipolar, okay bipolar, okay?
Okay, all right read, okay
Such a fucking asshole he hates this quote
You know what then dude and
is a fucking anonymous asshole that's not very high IQ.
Dude that just came and skewered this Ensler,
which he's white, he's a slow white one,
I'll tell you that.
He's definitely correct.
He shouldn't say that.
I will ask you one last time.
You mean five fucking,
not one where you can crack her?
Can you, nigger, crack her.
Hey, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay,
what the fuck, sorry, sorry, okay, bye.
Okay, bye, you ruined it, sorry.
Sorry, dude.